Gavin Sutton

〒981-3331 宮城県富谷市東向陽台三丁目25-15 Phone: 090-2955-6511

Email: gavinsutton6511@gmail.com

Summary

Previous English Instructor with 2+ years working and 4+ years living in Japan now seeking work in Web Development roles. Experience with the office work environment, communicating in Japanese and creating my own work.

Coming from an educational background in IT I hope to use my abilities, learn more skills, and succeed in a new line of work.

Education

Oak Bay High School

Graduated 2011

Camosun College

2011 - 2012: Computer Systems Technology

2013 - 2016: General Studies

University of Victoria

2016 - 2018: Computer Science

Miyagi International Association (宮城県国際化協会)

May 2018 - March 2019: Studying Japanese part-time

Sendai International School of Japanese (仙台国際日本語学校)

April 2022 - June 2022: Studying Japanese part-time

Skills

- Strengths in CSS, HTML and JavaScript
- Basic knowledge of Python, Java, and SQL
- Strong organizational and planning skills
- Presenting new concepts in an easy to understand way
- Able to provide helpful, clear and attentive customer service

Work Experience

Position: English Instructor

Company: 仙台市青葉少年少女発明クラブ

June 2018 - March 2019

• Giving brief, concise English lessons

• Working with children in English to build inventions

• Planning activities with a team of other teachers

Position: English Instructor **Company:** ステージライン 仙台校 January 2019 - November 2019

• Giving group and private English lessons

• Providing an enjoyable atmosphere in and outside of the classroom

• Developing lessons for a variety of levels and personalities

Position: English Instructor

Company: Kids Duo(キッズデュオ)

March 2020 - March 2021

• Teaching English to large classrooms of children

• Creating my own lessons to provide fun and education

• Work closely with coworkers in a fast-paced environment